(this.webpackJsonplemonade=this.webpackJsonplemonade||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,,,,,,function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/lucas.25b31e84.svg"},,function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(26)},,,,,function(e,t,a){},,,function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),r=a.n(n),s=a(6),o=a.n(s),i=(a(17),a(4)),c=a(3),l=a(1),u=a(2),h=a.n(u),m=(a(20),function(e){var t=e.name,a=e.onClick,n=e.className,s=void 0===n?"button":n;return r.a.createElement("button",{className:s,onClick:a,type:"button"},t)}),d=a(9),f=function(e){var t=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:{};return Object(d.number_with_delimiter)(e,t)},g=a(10),w=a.n(g),p=(a(21),function(e){var t=e.mode,a=e.score,n=e.onStart,s="end"===t,o=s?"Try again":"Start";return r.a.createElement("div",{className:h()("salute",{"salute-end":s})},!s&&r.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-triangle-bg"}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-content"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-content-image"},r.a.createElement("img",{className:"thumb-up",src:w.a,alt:"lucas"})),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-content-text"},s&&r.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-content-suptitle"},"Total score:"),r.a.createElement("h1",{className:"content-title"},s?r.a.createElement("span",null,"$",f(a)," earned"):r.a.createElement("span",null,"Who wants to be a millionaire?")),r.a.createElement(m,{name:o,onClick:n}))))}),b=(a(22),function(e){var t=e.answerState,a=e.answer,n=e.onSubmit,s=e.variantMarker;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:h()("game-button",t.answer===a&&{selected:t.selected,correct:t.correct,wrong:t.wrong}),onClick:function(){return n(a)}},r.a.createElement("span",{className:"variant"},s),r.a.createElement("span",{className:"text"},a))}),v=(a(23),function(e){var t=e.isModalOpen,a=e.children,n=e.onClick;return Object(s.createPortal)(r.a.createElement("div",{className:"modal"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"modal-backdrop",onClick:function(){return n(!t)}}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"modal-content"},a)),document.getElementById("modal-root"))}),E=(a(24),function(e){var t=e.priseList,a=e.step;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"prise-list"},t.map((function(e,t){return r.a.createElement("div",{key:e,className:h()("prise-button",{"prise-button-earned":t<a,"prise-button-active":t===a})},"$",f(e))})))}),k=(a(25),["A","B","C","D"]),q=function(e){var t=e.currentQuestion,a=e.answerState,s=e.priseList,o=e.step,i=e.onSubmit,l=Object(n.useState)(!1),u=Object(c.a)(l,2),m=u[0],d=u[1];return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"game"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:h()("toggle",{"toggle-open":m}),onClick:function(){return d(!m)}},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"toggle-bar1"}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"toggle-bar2"}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"toggle-bar3"})),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-content"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-question"},r.a.createElement("h1",null,t.question)),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-buttons"},t.answers.map((function(e,t){return r.a.createElement(b,{key:t,answer:e,answerState:a,onSubmit:i,variantMarker:k[t]})})))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-prises"},r.a.createElement(E,{priseList:s,step:o}))),m&&r.a.createElement(v,{isModalOpen:m,onClick:d},r.a.createElement(E,{priseList:s,step:o})))},y=a(11),O=["hello","cat","cool","dude","McFly"],S={500:[{id:1,question:"Who wasn't a member of the Beatles?",corrects:["Justin Timberlake"],answers:["John Lennon","Paul McCartney","Ringo Star"]},{id:1,question:"Which website is the most popular search engine?",corrects:["Google"],answers:["DuckDuckGo","Myspace","Bing"]},{id:1,question:"What is the smallest unit of American currency?",corrects:["Penny"],answers:["Dime","Quarter","Dollar"]}],1e3:[{id:2,question:"In which sport do two teams pull at the opposite ends of a rope?",corrects:["Tug of war"],answers:["Basketball","Ice hockey","Polo"]},{id:2,question:"What is the first word in the phonetic alphabet?",corrects:["Alpha"],answers:["Apple","Armadillo","Amazon"]},{id:2,question:"In the novel 'The Lord of The Ring', Frodo, Sam and Bilbo come from which region of Middle Earth?",corrects:["The Shire"],answers:["The Green","The Borough","The City"]}],2e3:[{id:3,question:"Where does a cowboy wear chaps?",corrects:["On his legs"],answers:["On his head","On his arms","On his hands"]},{id:3,question:"Which of these means a speech in a play where a character talks to themselves rather than to other characters?",corrects:["Soliloquy"],answers:["Interlude","Revue","Chorus"]},{id:3,question:"In the 'Transformers' film franchise, who is the leader of the Decepticons?",corrects:["Megatron"],answers:["Megaphone","Megabyte","Megabus"]}],4e3:[{id:4,question:"Which of these zodiac signs is not represented by an animal with horns?",corrects:["Aquarius"],answers:["Taurus","Capricorn","Aries"]},{id:4,question:"Which is a Mexican stuffed, fried pancake?",corrects:["Taco"],answers:["Waco","Saki","Pesto"]}],8e3:[{id:5,question:"Sherpas and Gurkhas are native to which country?",corrects:["Nepal"],answers:["Morocco","Ecuador","Russia"]},{id:5,question:"Which of these words means confused language or technical terminology?",corrects:["Jargon"],answers:["Jardin","Jarhead","Jamjar"]}],16e3:[{id:6,question:"'Escape' or 'Die Frying' is a tagline for which film?",corrects:["Chicken Run"],answers:["Ratatouille","Free Willy","Babe"]},{id:6,question:"Which of these is a 2003 Disney computer-animated film?",corrects:["Locating Remo"],answers:["Discovering Lemo","Unearthing Zemo","Finding Nemo"]}],32e3:[{id:7,question:"What is the name of the world\u2019s highest active volcano?",corrects:["Cotopaxi"],answers:["St Helens","Etna","Krakatoa"]},{id:7,question:"According to the Highway Code, what shape is the standard sign giving the order to 'Stop'?",corrects:["Octagon"],answers:["Pentagon","Hexagon","Heptagon"]}],64e3:[{id:8,question:"Which of these books is believed to have been inspired by the real-life experiences of the Scottish sailor Alexander Selkirk?",corrects:["Robinson Crusoe"],answers:["Moby Dick","The Count of Monte Cristo","Treasure Island"]},{id:8,question:"What was the nickname of Dr Leonard McCoy in the original series of 'Star Trek'?",corrects:["Bones"],answers:["Jaws","Head","Gums"]},{id:8,question:"Who was Brad Pitt's partner in the 1995 film 'Se7en'?",corrects:["Morgan Freeman"],answers:["Keanu Reeves","Bruce Willis","Matt Damon"]}],125e3:[{id:9,question:"The 2002 Booker Prize winner was Yan Martel's 'Life of ...'",corrects:["Pi"],answers:["Po","Pee","Pum"]},{id:9,question:"Who gave their name to a continent?",corrects:["Amerigo Vespucci"],answers:["Europa Bellini","Africo Tintorini","Asio Canelli"]}],25e4:[{id:10,question:"The young of which creature is known as a squab?",corrects:["Pigeon"],answers:["Salmon","Horse","Octopus"]},{id:10,question:"Which is a South American capital city?",corrects:["Cayenne"],answers:["Paprika","Mustard","Saffron"]}],5e5:[{id:11,question:"An insect\u2019s hard outer skeleton is made mainly of what substance?",corrects:["Chitin"],answers:["Keratin","Glycogen","Lignin"]},{id:11,question:"Which 2002 Tom Hanks film had the tagline, 'Every father is a hero to his son'?",corrects:["Road to Perdition"],answers:["Road to Zanzibar","Road to Glory","Road to Morocco"]}],1e6:[{id:12,question:"In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?",corrects:["Blackbeard"],answers:["Captain Kidd","Calico Jack","Bartholomew Roberts"]},{id:12,question:"Which scientific unit is named after an Italian nobleman?",corrects:["Volt"],answers:["Ohm","Hertz","Pascal"]},{id:12,question:"Who was the first man to travel into space twice?",corrects:["Gus Grissom"],answers:["Vladimir Titov","Michael Collins","Yuri Gagarin"]}]},N=Object(l.keys)(S),j=["start","end"],C={answer:"",wrong:!1,correct:!1,selected:!1},M=function(){return new Promise((function(e){setTimeout((function(){e()}),500)}))},W=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)({}),t=Object(c.a)(e,2),a=t[0],s=t[1],o=Object(n.useState)(0),u=Object(c.a)(o,2),h=u[0],m=u[1],d=Object(n.useState)("start"),f=Object(c.a)(d,2),g=f[0],w=f[1],b=Object(n.useState)(C),v=Object(c.a)(b,2),E=v[0],k=v[1];Object(n.useEffect)((function(){if(h<N.length){var e=function(e){var t,a=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:500,n=Object(l.shuffle)(e[a])[0],r=n.answers,s=n.corrects,o=n.question,i=Object(l.shuffle)(s)[0];if(r.length<3){var c=Object(l.shuffle)(O);t=new Array(3-r.length).fill(null).map((function(e,t){return c[t]})).concat(r)}r.length>=3&&(t=Object(l.take)(Object(l.shuffle)(r),3));var u=Object(l.shuffle)([].concat(Object(y.a)(t),[i]));return{question:o,correct:i,answers:u}}(S,N[h]);s(e)}}),[h]);return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,j.includes(g)&&r.a.createElement(p,{mode:g,score:h?N[h-1]:"0",onStart:function(){w("game"),m(0)}}),"game"===g&&r.a.createElement(q,{priseList:N,step:h,currentQuestion:a,answerState:E,onSubmit:function(e){k(Object(i.a)(Object(i.a)({},E),{},{answer:e,selected:!0}));var t=e.includes(a.correct),n=h===N.length-1;M().then((function(){t?(k((function(e){return Object(i.a)(Object(i.a)({},e),{},{selected:!1,correct:!0})})),M().then((function(){k(C),m(h+1),n&&w("end")}))):(k((function(e){return Object(i.a)(Object(i.a)({},e),{},{selected:!1,wrong:!0})})),M().then((function(){k(C),w("end")})))}))}}))};o.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(W,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}],[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.da25c03f.chunk.js.map